https://indobatiks.com/return-and-privacy-policies

Clearance
Batik PaintingsCotton Batik FabricsPrecuts- Cotton Batik Fabrics
Fashion Patterns
Accessories & Craft PatternsEco-Friendly Reusable Food WrapsGarments for SaleEmbellished BatiksBatik Cards
All products are while supplies last.Returns
We hope that customers are happy with their purchases. However, any unaltered item may be returned for any reason for a merchandise refund for up to 30 days from the date of purchase. Refunds will be credited to the account used for purchase.
Returns of $300 or more will be assessed a restocking fee.
Indonesian Batiks Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Indonesian Batiks. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Indonesian Batiks collects, and the ways in which indobatiks.com uses that personal information. We will never sell your information to any other party.
Where Indonesian Batiks discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use the personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Indonesian Batiks may disclose your personal information to the extent required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.Personal Information Collection
Indonesian Batiks may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:
Information about your use of this website
Information that you provide the purpose of registering with the website
Information about transactions carried out over this website
Information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services
Any other information that you send to Indonesian Batiks
Using Personal Information
Indonesian Batiks may use your personal information to:
Administer this website
Personalize the website for you
Enable your access to and use of the website services
Send you products that you purchase
Utilize your information for sending communications to you
Send you statements and invoices
Collect payments from you
Securing Your Data
Indonesian Batiks will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
indobatiks.com will store all the personal information you provide on its PCI compliant secure servers.
Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.
Updating this Statement
indobatiks.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
Other websites
This website may contain links to other websites. indobatiks.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.
Batik PaintingsCotton Batik FabricsPrecuts- Cotton Batik Fabrics
Accessories & Craft PatternsEco-Friendly Reusable Food WrapsGarments for SaleEmbellished BatiksBatik Cards
